Guide to the New-York Historical Society Collection of New York City Miscellaneous Manuscripts, circa 1614-1933 (bulk 1641-1900) MS 443.19
New-York Historical Society
- Letter from Joseph Hawley, Caleb Strong, Tim Edwards, Theo Sedgwick, Massachusetts Commissioner, to Hon. Philip Schuyler, Esq. and Gerard Banken, Esq., 1784 November 2 (Box 5, Folder 73)
  Letter regarding property line and survey
- Certification by Daniel Dunscomb, New York Merchant, of removal of lead, 1784 December 10 (Box 5, Folder 72)
  850 pounds of lead for public service was taken out of the house of Peter Van Brugh Livingston of Hanover Square
- Document in the Case, Thomas Grant v. the Estate of Lodorvick Bamper regarding debt of 1772 pounds, 1785 October 12 (Box 5, Folder 59)
- Paymaster General John Pierce's Report of August 10, 1785 (Copied), RE: Frenchman Pierre Regnier de Rousse to for depreciation because he was a foreigner (Box 5, Folder 59)
- Acknowledgment by John Fairlee that John Sauderse deposited a certificate in the Commissioner's Office signed by William Van Ingen, 1785 January 26 (Box 5, Folder 59)
- Petition regarding drawing back of duty taxes on re-exported goods, by 11 New York Merchants, 1786 (Box 5, Folder 55)
  11 merchants includes John Vanderbilt, Anthony Bleeker, James Watson, James Greenleaf, Robert and George Lewis, John Pintard, Isaac Clason, Jose Rois Silva, Stewart & Jones
- Receipt by John Lansing that Henry Hay, State Agent, had given him $100.00, 1786 May 23 (Box 5, Folder 54)
- Letter from James Vernon to Stewart & Jones, 1786 April 1 (Box 5, Folder 56)
  Give Capt. Mercedes the freight to deliver to Albany
- Discharge of John Denny from Debtor's Prison, 1786 June 24 (Box 5, Folder 57)
- Certificate of Damaged Goods (4 tons of hemp) sold at public auction for 150 pounds, signed by William Heyer and August Lawrence, Port Wardens, 1786 October 4 (Box 5, Folder 58)
  The damaged goods were owned by Stewart & Jones, Merchants, on a ship from London
- 1786 True Copy Census Document Schedule of the Citizens & Inhabitants in the State of New York by county/ 1975 Number of Electors in the State of New York by county, 1786/1795 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  Categories for Census: Males under 16, Males over 16 under 60, Males over 60, Females under 16, females over 16, Slaves (males/females), Indians who pay tax/ Electors are broken down by Freehold values and electors who were Freemen by a certain date
- List of Houses surveyed and insured by the Insurance Office, 1787 (Box 5, Folder 46)
  Almost three hundred houses listed with names and addresses
- Sheriff M. Willett's Calendar of Prisoners in the Jail of the City and County of New York, 1787 August 6 (Box 5, Folder 60)
  6 prisoners were held. All laborers for burglary, theft, robbing on the high way, robbery
- Mayor's Court Directive to the sheriff to take into custody John Aspinell, 1787 August 22 (Box 5, Folder 60)
  Aspinell "lives on Prince Street across from new sugar factory"
- Extracts from Journal of Manassak Cutler describing City Hall, 1787 (Box 5, Folder 60)
  Appears to be written copy of journal describing what City Hall looked like. 1873 Feb. 24 Public Library of Cincinnati
- Inquisition by Sheriff M. Willett regarding damages that James Cox suffered., 1787 December (Box 5, Folder 60)
  Damages came to 44 pounds, signed by Willet and jurors
- List of Grand Jurors containing 25 names, 1787-1789 (Box 5, Folder 61)
  One list for 1787 and one list for 1789, both lists contain about 25 names
- A Plan of the Descent of St. James Street from Bowry Lane to Cherry Street drawn by Evert Blancher, Jr. and John McComb, City Surveyors, 1787 June 27 (Box 5, Folder 63)
- Letter from James Montaudevert to Stewart & Jones regarding delivery to Capt. Stephens of Ship Pretty, 1787 March 27 (Box 5, Folder 63)
  Deliver to Capt. Stephens anything he will ask you for
- Letter from Jeremiah Manning of Bonum Town, New Jersey, to Stewart & Jones regarding need for rigging for a sloop, 1787 March 14 (Box 5, Folder 63)
- Letter from Henry Kuhl on behalf of Michael Hillegas, Treasurer, to Nathaniel Gilman, Esq. regarding sending books to the Treasurer, 1787 December 11 (Box 5, Folder 63)
  Send remainder directly to Honorable Board of Treasury to save postage
- Results of Election of Delegates to the Convention in Poughkeepsie, signed by Richard Varick, Recorder, and Aldermen of the City of New York, 1788 May 29 (Box 5, Folder 51)
  John Jay, Richard Morris, John Sloss Hobart, Alexander Hamilton, Robert Livingston, Isaac Roosevelt, James Duane, Richard Harison and Nicholas Low were delegates
- Report on James Hughes' (Notary Public) Investigation of the Books of the Treasury Department of the United States, 1788 April 30 (Box 5, Folder 52)
- Decision by Jury that Property of the vessel Brig. Nymph belongs to Henry Hay not to John Quail, 1788 April 26 (Box 5, Folder 53)
  Signed by all 12 jurors
- List of 46 Members who attended the First Congress of the United States under the New Constitution, 1789 (Box 5, Folder 49)
- Summons from Benjamin Blagge, Alderman, for Jacob Lawrence to appear, 1789 January 24 (Box 6, Folder 14)
- Regulation of Greenwich Street between Barclay and Murray Streets drawn by Evert Bancher, Jr. and John McComb, City Surveyors, 1789 June 3 (Box 5, Folder 50)
  Owners of lots noted
- Names of proprietors by lot along Chatham Street, 1789 July (Box 5, Folder 45)
- Acknowledgment by David Devoor of New Rochelle of Debt to New York State in the amount of Ten pounds, 1789 July 13 (Box 5, Folder 48)
  Richard Varick, Recorder of the City of New York signed document
- Agreement between Hodge, Allen & Campbell, Booksellers, and William Robins that Robins may have front parlour in house on Maiden Lane, closet on second floor (Large enough for bed) and cellar and yard. Also William Robins may work in printing business, 1790 May 1 (Box 5, Folder 38)
  1 year lease for 15 pounds; Salary of five dollars per week
- Amount of Insolvents by name in South Ward, 1790 May 18 (Box 5, Folder 38)
- Amount of Insolvents by name in Dock Ward, 1790 May 17 (Box 5, Folder 38)
- Petition of John Bartolf to Mayor of New York (Richard Varick) to drive cart, 1790 April 26 (Box 5, Folder 39)
  Unable to learn trade because of War but fought against invaders
- Two subscription notices for the New York Magazine or Literary Repository, 1790 May 17; 1791 March (Box 5, Folder 40)
  One notice lists the subscribers and addresses. Subscription price was 18 shillings per year
- Indenture signed by Michael Roche acknowledging debt of 30 pounds, 1790 January 7 (Box 5, Folder 41)
- Sworn testimony of Evert Blancher, Jr. is just and true -- appeared before Nicholas Bayard, 1790 November 20 (Box 5, Folder 42)
- Inquisition held at house of John Simmons, signed by Sheriff Robert Boyd and jurors, 1790 September 13 (Box 5, Folder 42)
- Table for the Assize of Loaf Bread -- Common Council of New York City, 1790 February 15 (Box 5, Folder 43)
  Table for the Assize of Loaf Bread regulated the size of bread sold
- Extracts from the minutes of the Common Council of New York City, 1790 April and May (Box 5, Folder 44)
  Items involved paving Broadway from Lutheran Church to Vesey Street, Contracting with Elias Burger to do work on Wharf, Consideration of best use of Common Lands
- 1790 -1798 Rates of Medical Charges by the Physicians of New York (Box 5, Folder 47)
  Includes charges for first consultation, night visit after ten o'clock, extracting a tooth, opening an absyss, amputation, removing a cataract, hair loss
- Rates of Medical Charges by Practitioners of Physics and Surgery in the City of New York, 1790 (Box 5, Folder 47)
  Includes charges for verbal advice, written advice, visits, visits with a single dose of medicine
- Sworn affidavit of Jane Highland, 1792 August 21 (Box 5, Folder 32)
  Highland testified against James King
- Memorial of Gerard Banker, Treasurer of the State of New York, 1792 (Box 5, Folder 35)
- Return of Mayor as part of Canvassers appointed to canvas and estimate votes in the 1792 Election (Box 5, Folder 37)
  Election of Governor and Lieutenant Governor is George Clinton and Pierre Van Cortlandt; Henry Cruger, John Schenck, and Selah Strong are senators for Southern District; Joseph Hasbrouck is senator from Middle District and John Frey is senator from Western District; Robert Woodworth and John Livingston are senators from Eastern District
- Contemporaneous Account of Panic of 1792 by Miss C. Wynkoop (?) (Box 6, Folder 16)
- Document announcing result of election for members of the State Assembly, signed by Richard Varick, Mayor, and Aldermen of the City of New York, 1793 May 29 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  Jonathan Post, John Delancey, William Willcocks, Josiah Ogden Hoffman, James Watson, Richard Furman and Robert Boyd elected.
- Sworn statement by John Hinton that William Collins, a 13-year old prisoner aboard the Concord Frigate is from Philadelphia and must be returned to his mother, signed by Richard Varick, Mayor, 1793 September 9 (Box 5, Folder 30)
- Sheriff M. Willett's calendar of prisoners confined in the jail of the city and county of New York, 1793 January 15 (Box 5, Folder 30)
  Gives names, crimes, dates, by whom committed to jail, remarks. Crimes are forgery, swindling, murder, larceny, and paping, counterfeit money
- Oct. 11, 1793 resolution Common Council of New York City to provide $5,000 to the poor and most distressed citizens of Philadelphia after their great calamity, undated (Box 5, Folder 30)
- Letter from Col. N. Rochester to George Gale, Esquire, Supervisor of the Revenue, 1793 July 16 (Box 5, Folder 31)
  Doctor Schmibly's amount is very moderate, send $200
- List of articles purchased for Government house, 1793 February 1 (Box 5, Folder 34)
- Pages from Custom House Register regarding goods on vessels and amounts of Duties, 1793 (Box 5, Folder 36)
  Vessels include Schooner Waterford, Ann and Susan, Brig. Nancy, Sloop Swallow, Brig. Harriot, Ship Fanny, Brig Eliza, Ship Liberty, Sloop Charles, Brig. Recovery; The Masters were from Cork, St. Croix, Port au Prince, Curacao, Portsmouth, Havre de Grace, Cadiz, St. Eustatia, Cape Francois, Waterford
- Tribute by John Franklin, H. Mulligan, Ezekiel Robins, certifying that Mrs. Wheton, Mrs. Todd, Mrs. Whaley, widows, great service to American Prisoners, thanked by General Washington, 1794 February 24 (Box 5, Folder 64)
- Incomplete Recognizance of James Watt; not completed or signed, 1794 December 3 (Box 5, Folder 74)
- Letter from Democratic Society of New York to Democratic Society of Pennsylvania, 1795 (Box 5, Folder 75)
  Refuse to surrender our rights to thought and speech
- Petition to Legislature of New York of the Subscribers Repackers of Beef and Pork, 1795 February 11 (Box 5, Folder 76)
  Petition to receive one shilling per barrel packed
- Agreement of Aldermen and the City of New York to Establish an Office of the Police at City Hall, 1795 October 26 (Box 6, Folder 17)
- Pages 183-186 of Letterbook kept by unknown French Merchant (in French), 1795 July 7-11 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  Letters concern trade with Mr. Olive, trade in coffee, a trip to Philadelphia
- Acknowledgment by The Governors of the New York Hospital of expenses paid by Legislature, need for additional funds, 1796 February 18 (Box 6, Folder 2)
- Report of the New York Society for Promoting the Manumission of Slaves, 1797 May (Box 6, Folder 3)
  School, Citizens are using Danish Flag to supply foreign nations with slaves against the Act of Congress
- New York City Inquisition at the Dwelling of Catherine Simmons, Innkeeper, 1797 April 14 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  $35.00 in damages; signed by Sheriff John Lansing and 12 jurors
- Hay Receipt, 1797 February 27 (Box 6, Folder 7)
- 1797 Roster of Firemen in Engine Company 20 (Box 6, Folder 19)
- Receipted Certificate of Debt to the United States, 1798 February 10 (Box 5, Folder 33)
  Daniel Cotton and Thomas Butler acknowledgement of $400 owed to the United States
- Certification of Joint Commission in Regulating Elections that John Jay was elected Governor and Stephen Van Rensselaer elected Lt. Governor, 1798 June 12 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  David Gelston, Dewitt Clinton, William Denning, Richard Hatfield, Ambrose Spencer, Ebenezer Foote, Leonard Gansevoort, John Sanders, Thomas Gold, John Frey, Frederick Getman, William Beekman, and Jacob Morris – Senators
- Militia Rolls - 7 Undersigned (captains, lieutenants, ensigns) Swear to support the US Constitution, undated (Box 6, Folder 5)
- State of New York Allegiance Book, 1798-1802 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  Undersign swear their allegiance to the State of New York and to support the US Constitution, renounce any allegiance to foreign kings
- Testimony of Peter Duschent, Prisoner in City Jail, re prisoner William Foulk who tried to break out of jail, 1798 August 8 (Box 6, Folder 5)
- Testimony of Richard Smith, Turnkey of City Jail, re prisoner William Foulk who tried to break out of jail, 1798 August 8 (Box 6, Folder 5)
- Supervisor's Office, District of New York document RE: Duties on Rum secured, 1798 February 6 (Box 6, Folder 5)
- Elizabeth Dungree's Consent and Covenant re Dock at New Slip. Lots conveyed to James Roosevelt, 1798 March 19 (Box 6, Folder 5)
- Contract for Building the Dock at New Slip, 1798 May 7 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  Document in case James Roosevelt v. Harry Peters, James C. Roosevelt (Exec. of Abner Dungee, deceased with Justice Deerman
- Articles of Agreement for filling in the Dock, 1798 May 30 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  Document in case James Roosevelt v. Harry Peters, James C. Roosevelt (Exec. of Abner Dungee, deceased with Henry Sharmon
- Sworn statement that articles imported by Joseph Harris on Sloop Two Sisters are for his use and not for sale, 1798 September 10 (Box 6, Folder 8)
- Issues of the Luptonian and Abstracts which contain copies of letters of William Lupton regarding the Yellow Fever Epidemic of 1798, undated (Box 6, Folder 10)
- 1798 Anniversary Oration on Education before the Association of Teachers of New York City, by Jonathan Fisk (Box 6, Folder 20)
- Manhattan Tragedy – or Curvin and Elma, An Historic Ballad of 1799, undated (Box 6, Folder 6)
  Verses were written based upon disappearance of a woman named Sands and her alleged murderer Levi Weeks on Dec. 22, 1799. Her body was found a few weeks later in the Manhattan Well
- Letter from Richard Harison, Esq., Recorder of the City of New York, to Sheriff of New York re attachment against the estate of John Saunders, 1799 June 27 (Box 6, Folder 9)
- Letter from Richard Harison, Esq., Recorder of the City of New York, to Sheriff of New York re attachment against Oliver Phelps, 1799 December 18 (Box 6, Folder 9)
- Sworn statements by Captain Daniel Braine and John Barker that Ship Fanny did not go through any French port, 1799 December 18 (Box 6, Folder 10)
- List of 64 persons summoned by Attorney General, Ogden Hoffman, as witnesses on behalf of the people in court case, 1799 August 8 (Box 6, Folder 10)
- Discharge of of debt because of insolvency for John Moffits, 1799 April 4 (Box 6, Folder 10)
- Request from Captain Hughes of Brig Friends to Sheriff to liberate Thomas Conly, 1799 June 11 (Box 6, Folder 10)
- Notes taken from New York Gazette and other journals (1799-1807) regarding the erection of the Mechanics Hall, undated (Box 6, Folder 15)
- Deposition of James Townsend who hired Charles Gillard to deliver a cartload of iron to basin, 1800 July 19 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  Document in the case of The People v. Carles Gillard in Police Court of New York City
- A True Copy of 1800 Demand to Keeper of the Jail to deliver Mr. William McCready, New York Merchant and Bankrupt, to answer questions, undated (Box 6, Folder 44)
- City of New York c. 1800 Assessment for Digging out and Filling in Broadway from Arch Bridge to Prince Street, undated (Box 6, Folder 45)
  Lists property owners by east and west side of Broadway
- Articles of Agreement among Theophilus Beekman, party of the first part, Fletcher W. Beekman, party of the second part, and John Townsend and Walter Franklin, merchants of the third part, 1800 April 24 (Box 6, Folder 46)
  Merchants will pay sum of money to Beekman that said lots of ground amount to
- Owner or Consignee's (Adrian Van Linderen) oath upon entering of merchandise – Port of New York, signed Joshua Sands, Collector, 1800 May 2 (Box 6, Folder 47)
  For Ship Hare
- Order for the Sale of Some Property Seized by the Sheriff of New York by an attachment, signed Richard Harris, Recorder of New York, 1800 September 4 (Box 6, Folder 47)
  Property of Lewis Gruin consisted of shingles, pipe staves and hogshead staves
- Certificate signed by Jasper Hopper, District Secretary of the State of New York, 1800 December 22 (Box 6, Folder 48)
  Certification RE: Jacob Ramson, formerly Private in 2nd Regiment issued lot of 600 acres
- Indenture of James Stevens to apprentice to Henry Kenyon, Mariner, 1800 September 17 (Box 7, Folder 17)
- Petition of Isaac Winans and Christian White to Richard Harris, Recorder of the City of New York, for attachment of Brig. Hero, 1800 November 29 (Box 6, Folder 49)
- Agreement to build pier between Fly and Coffeehouse Slips by Proprietors of Lots on South Street, 1801 June 20 (Box 6, Folder 30)
- Oaths for Registers; Custom House Papers, 1802 (Box 5, Folder 36)
  1. Sworn Statement (1802 November 10) that vessel Sincerity of New York is owned by Elias Burger and David Rogers and that David Rogers is the captain; 2. Sworn statement (1802 October 6) that vessel Hannah Bartley of New York is owned by Joseph Gotier and he is captain; 3. Sworn statement (1802 October 7) that vessel Sincerity of New York is owned by David Rogers and Elias Burger and that David Rogers is captain of the vessel
- Return of Captain Nicholas Lawrence's Watchmen from third Monday in January to third Monday in February, 1802, 1802 January - February (Box 6, Folder 38)
  List of names, ages, occupation, birthplace, and address
- Limits to Jail as laid down by Mangin, City Surveyor, 1802 July (Box 6, Folder 39)
  Plan showing limits to perimeter of jail
- Official letter from John B. Prevost, City Recorder, to Sheriff RE: John Stockdale, 1802 September 8 (Box 6, Folder 40)
- Affidavit of Clerk of Stores, re: property of Henry Cruger's estate, 1803 January 22 (Box 4, Folder 47)
  By clerk of stores which were the property of the estate of Henry Cruger, Esquire (Mr. Alex Stewart left clerk in charge of the stores); British took possession of city; persons took stores while clerk was imprisoned
- Mayor's Office of the City of New York List of Deaths from Yellow Fever from July to October 1803, 1803 July - October (Box 6, Folder 24)
  Deaths reached 615; Document divided by Month, Day, Week Day, Cases, Deaths
- Memorandum of Interments in the City of New York 1803-1806, by John Pintard (Box 6, Folder 42)
- Petition of the Marshalls and Constables of the City of New York to the Legislature of New York State regarding inadequate compensation, 1803 January 28 (Box 6, Folder 43)
- Certificate Showing the Safe Shipment of 21 Bales of Cotton on Brig Eleanor, signed by John Hodgkins, 1803 April 29 (Box 6, Folder 61)
- Poll Statement of Votes Taken in Ninth Ward, City of New York, 1804 November 20, 25 (Box 6, Folder 25)
  Abraham King was elected Alderman, Jacob Shute was elected Assistant, also elections for Assessors, Collector, and Constables
- Draft of Report from Committee appointed to examine the best mode of supplying the City of New York with adequate water, 1804 August 27 (Box 6, Folder 26)
  Supply adequate water not only for culinary and domestic purposes but also for fire; suggestion of dam and reservoir
- Order to the Owners of 143 Water Street from Common Council of New York City, 1804 June 4 (Box 6, Folder 31)
  State of Nuisance, cause cellar to be raised with pure earth at least four inches
- Office of Public HealthList of People Killed by Malignant Fever in September and October of 1805, 1805 September - October (Box 6, Folder 27)
  Includes names, addresses, and dates
- 3 Documents – 1. Charles Innis Certificate of Seaman and US Citizen under Act for Relief and Protection of American Seamen; Certificate for Debenture of Brig Fair Manhattan; Report of Births of May 1805, 1805 May 20; 1805 May 28; 1805 May 25 (Box 6, Folder 29)
  The Brig Fair was carrying brandy, wine, oil, vermicelli and macaroni; Birth record page has columns for white, black, free and slaves
- Militia Roll and Enlistment of Light Infantry by Commander Micah Brooks, 1806 June 15 (Box 6, Folder 30)
- Certification that James Smith has been received in to 7th Company, by Commander John Minuse of 7th Company of the Second Regiment, 1806 May 28 (Box 6, Folder 30)
- Letters from J.H. Mattau to Philip Unger re purchase of cargo from sloop, 1806 (Box 6, Folder 30)
- Plan by the Corporation of the City of New York to extended Piers into East River between Exchange and Whitehall Slips, 1806 May 2 (Box 6, Folder 30)
- Arrangements made by the City's Inspector's Office for Keeping the Peace for This and Tomorrow Evenings, 1806 December 31 (Box 6, Folder 30)
- Memorial of the Inhabitants of the City of New York, Committee of Defense's Document regarding the Defense of New York, 1806 March 21 (Box 6, Folder 30)
  Long list of signatures
- The Fortification and Defense of New York City by The Memorial of the Inhabitants of the City of New York, Committee of Defense, 1807 (Box 6, Folder 21)
  Outline of Fort Columbus in New York Harbor; Discussions re Defense of New York Harbor; Minutes of Committee of Defense meetings; 4 projects for Defending New York – 1. By Governor Morgan, 2. By Col. Jonathon Williams, 3. Dr. Joseph Young, 4. By George W. Chapman, Esq.
- Petition of Lydia Heckler to Mayor Marinus Willett re license to carry on business of grocery and tavern after husband joined Miranda Expedition, 1807 May 16 (Box 6, Folder 32)
- Jacob Cholwell stated to John P. Ritter, Alderman of New York, that Abraham M. Griffin willfully broke lamp at corner of New Slip, 1807 March 24 (Box 6, Folder 33)
  Charge of $25.00
- Sworn statement of Isaac Wandle that Henry Mason was born at Guntuck, North Carolina, signed by William Popham, Notary Public, 1807 March 9 (Box 6, Folder 41)
- Map by William Bridges, City Surveyor, of Block of Ground in Nassau Street, 1807 June 17 (Box 6, Folder 41)
  Block of Ground on Nassau Street to ascertain property line between Mr. Mildeberger's and Mr. Walker's lots
- Commission of Pierre C. Van Wyck, Recorder of the City of New York, and Tunis Wortman, Clerk of the City of New York, by Daniel D. Tompkins, Governor of New York, 1808 February 8 (Box 6, Folder 23)
- Communication addressed by Mayor Dewitt Clinton on the subject of the Gambling House, No. 5 Murray Street, 1809 April 10 (Box 6, Folder 35)
  Called the house the "Road to Ruin"
- Power of Attorney from Alexander MacDonald to James Sackett to take possession of two lots., 1809 May 2 (Box 6, Folder 34)
- Note from the Bank Of New York, RE: Abraham Dunham for fifty dollars protested for non-payment, 1809 September 25 (Box 6, Folder 28)
  Note sent to Charles C. Williams
- Muster Roll of a Company of Light Artillery under Command of Capt. S.D. Townsend, 1809 October 1 (Box 6, Folder 22)
  List of names, ranks, and dates of Enlistment
- Office of Customs House's License to Carry on Coasting Trade for One Year, 1809 October 24 (Box 6, Folder 36)
  Lewis Smith of Marlborough with Sloop, named Wasp
- Two Thousand dollar Promissory Note of Luke Persiany to William Moore, 1810 June 20 (Box 6, Folder 62)
- Charter Party of Affreightment, witnessed by Henry Post, Cornelius Grinnel, Nathaniel Mintum, 1810 October 30 (Box 6, Folder 57)
  Ship Emolous
- Received from Waters Furman, Superintendant of the Streets, Pay for Carting and Sweeping, 1810 November 10 (Box 6, Folder 37)